{"RT_log_version":"1.0.1","RT_log_data":[{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.all.stat.show.126__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948072994410","data":{"timestamp":" 948072994410"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::Safari_Song__it_32","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073000740","data":{"timestamp":" 948073000740"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.ltr.lc:A..Z.all.asc.sim.stat.show.127__it_14","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073005625","data":{"timestamp":" 948073005625"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" null"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" null"," tutorId":" null"," matrixName":" null"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" null"," problemNumber":" 0"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 0"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" null"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073016937","data":{"timestamp":" 948073016936"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_3_1-3-6"," problemNumber":" 1"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 3"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073023482","data":{"timestamp":" 948073023482"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_2-11-6"," problemNumber":" 2"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073028400","data":{"timestamp":" 948073028400"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_9_9-11-13"," problemNumber":" 3"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 9"," userResponse":" 9"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073032443","data":{"timestamp":" 948073032442"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_8-2-6"," problemNumber":" 4"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073039091","data":{"timestamp":" 948073039091"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 11"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073045832","data":{"timestamp":" 948073045832"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_10-11-6"," problemNumber":" 5"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073051245","data":{"timestamp":" 948073051245"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_2_0-2-13"," problemNumber":" 6"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 2"," userResponse":" 2"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073055713","data":{"timestamp":" 948073055713"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_5_3-5-6"," problemNumber":" 7"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 5"," userResponse":" 5"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073059823","data":{"timestamp":" 948073059823"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 13"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073069070","data":{"timestamp":" 948073069069"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_4_3-4-13"," problemNumber":" 8"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 4"," userResponse":" 4"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073073171","data":{"timestamp":" 948073073170"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_0_0-2-11"," problemNumber":" 9"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 0"," userResponse":" 0"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073077697","data":{"timestamp":" 948073077697"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 3"," correctness":" INCORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073083518","data":{"timestamp":" 948073083518"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" null"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" 1"," substepProblem":" 1"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" 6"," userResponse":" 6"," correctness":" CORRECT"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 10"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"bpop.mn:0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073087795","data":{"timestamp":" 948073087794"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"type":"LOG_DATA","tutor":"story.hear::letters_alphabet_song__it_39","class":"INFO","tag":"PERFORMANCE_TAG","time":"948073093625","data":{"timestamp":" 948073093624"," userId":" 5B13002439"," sessionId":" 5B13002439_20000117_043622"," gameId":" 70f151fc-0fc2-45e0-912b-b376437f87f5"," language":" LANG_SW"," tutorName":" bubble_pop"," tutorId":" bpop.mn_0..9.MN-SD-UP-OFF2-BL1.incr.8"," matrixName":" math"," levelName":" null"," taskName":" BACKBUTTON"," problemName":" BPOP_6_3-12-6"," problemNumber":" 10"," substepNumber":" -1"," substepProblem":" 0"," attemptNumber":" 1"," expectedAnswer":" null"," userResponse":" null"," correctness":" null"," feedbackType":" null"," totalProblemsCount":" 0"," promotionMode":" PROMOTION"," scaffolding":" null"}},
{"end":"end"}]}